Rev. 07/2018

FACTS WHAT DOES BANKNORTHDO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Why? Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law givesconsumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell youhow we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefullyto understand what we do.

What? The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service youhave with us. This information can include:Social Security number and payment historyincome and transaction historyaccount balances and credit historyWhen you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described inthis notice.

How? All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everydaybusiness. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share theircustomers' personal information; the reasons BANKNORTH chooses to share; and whetheryou can limit this sharing.

Reasons we can share your personalinformation Does BANKNORTH share? Can you limit this sharing?

For our everyday business purposes–

such as to process your transactions, maintainyour account(s), respond to court orders andlegal investigations, or report to credit bureausYes No

For our marketing purposes–

to offer our products and services to you Yes No

For joint marketing with other financialcompanies No We don't share

For our affiliates' everyday business purposes–

information about your transactions andexperiencesNo We don't share

For our affiliates' everyday business purposes–

information about your creditworthiness No We don't share

For nonaffiliates to market to you No We don't share

Questions? Call 800-290-4306 or go to www.ibanknorth.com

PAGE 2

Who we are

Who is providing thisnotice?

BANKNORTH

What we do

How doesBANKNORTH protectmy personalinformation?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use securitymeasures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards andsecured files and buildings.We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this informationand limit access to those employees necessary.

How doesBANKNORTH collectmy personalinformation?

We collect your personal information, for example, when youopen an account or provide account informationapply for a loan or show your government-issued IDmake deposits or withdrawals from your accountWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates,or other companies.

Why can't I limit allsharing?

Federal law gives you the right to limit onlysharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about yourcreditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. Seebelow for more on your rights under state law.

Definitions

Affiliates Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial andnonfinancial companies.

BANKNORTH does not share with our affiliates.

Nonaffiliates Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial andnonfinancial companies.

BANKNORTH does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.

Joint marketing A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together marketfinancial products or services to you.

BANKNORTH doesn't jointly market.

Other important information

For North Dakota Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to marketto you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.

DEPOSIT PRO, Ver. 18.2.0.027 Copr. Finastra USA Corporation 1996, 2018. All Rights Reserved. ND - \- C:\APPS\CFI\TIS\PRIVDIS2
